Walter Melo

Web Developer / Designer

São Bernardo do Campo - SP - Brazil walmello24@gmail.com +55 11 99957-6409

I'm a Front End Developer and Web Designer with 3 years of experience in building intuitive, pixel perfect websites with Webflow. I'm a Javascript specialist with knowledge on diverse development tools and programming languages.

Work Experience

WEB DESIGNER AND DEVELOPER

Smartmentor

Design and Development of the landing page with Figma and Framer, Provide support to Front End developers

Jun 2023 - Jul 2024

WEBFLOW DEVELOPER

Eikon Labs

Design in Figma Participate in the entire development process in Webflow, provide support and maintenance for the development team.

May 2021 - Nov 2022

WEB DESIGNER

Freelancer

Time management, prioritizing of functionalities and briefing- Development and Design with Wordpress, Front End Development

Jul 2020 - Mai 2021

WEB DEVELOPER

42 Data Investments

Web development in PHP and Javascript and development of internal tools in C#,

Set 2019 - Fev 2020

Education

2023 - current University of People

Undergraduate Student Computer Science

Courses

Front End Development

Gama Academy - JUN 2020

UX Design

Gama Academy - DEC 2020

Webflow Layouts Certification Lv. 1

Webflow - APR 2022

Creative Web Design

Awwwards - JUL 2022

Skills

Development

HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Vue, GSAP, ThreeJS, Canvas

Design and No-code

Framer, Webflow, Zapier, Figma

Languages

Portuguese (Native) English (Fluent) Spanish (Intermediate)